Do you have a taste for terror? The suckers are back.
Fright Night Part 2 is a horror, comedy film directed by Tommy Lee Wallace.
After three years of therapy Charley Brewster, now a college student, is
convinced that Jerry Dandridge was a serial killer posing as a vampire.
But when Regine, a mysterious actress and her entourage move into Peter Vincent's
apartment block, the nightmare starts again - and this time it's personal!
Peter Vincent, played by Roddy McDowall.
Charley Brewster, played by William Ragsdale.
Alex, played by Traci Lind.
Regine Dandrige, played by Julie Carmen.
Louie, played by Jon Gries.
Belle, played by Russell Clark.
Fright Night Part 2 is a 1988 American supernatural horror film directed by
Tommy Lee Wallace, and a sequel to the 1985 film Fright Night.
Roddy McDowall and William Ragsdale reprise their roles as Peter Vincent and Charley
Brewster, alongside new cast members Traci Lind, Julie Carmen and Jon Gries.
Composer Brad Fiedel also returned with another distinct synthesizer score.
Following the plot of the first film, it focuses on Charley who, now a college student,
encounters a group of vampires led by a beautiful woman who is seeking him out.
Released by New Century/Vista in North America and TriStar Pictures elsewhere in 1989, the film grossed
almost $3 million domestically, and has since become a cult film like its predecessor.
In 2003, it received a brief issuing on DVD by Artisan Entertainment in a full frame presentation, but
the release quickly went out of print and has since become a rare collector's item.
Due to rights issues at the time, the film has not had a domestic home
video release since, but has become a common bootleg.
As of 2025 however, the rights have been cleared and a 4K/Blu-ray
release is set for release by Synapse Films in 2026.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.